Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
- OCAW (Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union), Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Target Health Hazards, 1972; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Author: OSHA (Occupational Health and Safety Administration)
    Notes: OSHA 2051
  - Item 3: To Eliminate Industrial Health Hazards, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Hydrogen Fluoride: Is It Dangerous?, 1974; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1977; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.10 (1977:Oct.)
  - Item 6: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1977; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.11/12 (1977:Nov./Dec.)
  - Item 7: Health Hazards in Plastics Manufacture, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1974; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Author: Sylvia Krekel
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1974:June). Noise: The Universal Menace
  - Item 9: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1974; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1974:June). Noise: The Universal Menace. Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1974; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1974:June). Noise: The Universal Menace. Copy 3.
  - Item 11: Alert: Hazards I: Asbestos, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1977; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1977:June)
  - Item 13: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1977; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1977:Apr.)
  - Item 14: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1977; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1977:Mar.)
  - Item 15: Lifelines: OCAW Health and Safety News, 1975; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.12 (1975:Dec.)
  - Item 16: Alert: OCAW Women: Some Ideas for Action, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Cooling It: The Problem of Heat in the Workplace, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: News from OCAW, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: News from OCAW, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Join 200,000 Workers!, 1979; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Fact book, 1978; Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: OCAW history & philosophy, Publication (Box 563, Folder 1)
    Author: Harvey O'Connor
- OCAW (Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union), Publication (Box 563, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: OCAW Reporter, 1992; Publication (Box 563, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.48:no.5/6 (1992:July/Aug.)
- OCAW (Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union), Publication (Box 563, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Group insurance plan for employees of OCAW, 1979; Publication (Box 563, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Resolutions adopted by the 21st Constitutional convention.., 1994; Publication (Box 563, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: OCAW Supports "Cradle to Grave" National Health Care: Pass It On. Information and speaker's manual, 1990; Publication (Box 563, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: OCAW Supports "Cradle to Grave" National Health Care: Pass It On. Information and speaker's manual, 1990; Publication (Box 563, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Standard Oil Co.: a report on our adversary, 1979; Publication (Box 563, Folder 3)
- IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers), Publication (Box 563, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: International Union of Operating Engineers: Contract No. 99-4-402-98-019-01: Final Report, Publication (Box 563, Folder 4)
    Author: IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers): U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: Learning By Doing
  - Item 2: Learning by Doing - One Hour Television Broadcast (transcript), Publication (Box 563, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 1982-84 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, 1982-1984 (Box 563, Folder 4)
    Notes: Copy 3
- IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers), Publication (Box 563, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: General Presidents' Project Maintenance agreement -- 1983 (2 copies, 1 is a photo copy), Publication (Box 563, Folder 5)
    Author: IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers)
  - Item 2: General Presidents' Project Maintenance agreement -- 1983 (2 copies, 1 is a photo copy), Publication (Box 563, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Cornell University and the International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 71-71A: March 15, 1984-March 14, 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 563, Folder 5)
    Author: IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers), Local 71-71A; Cornell University
  - Item 4: Agreement between Cornell University and the International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 71-71A: March 15, 1986-March 14, 1988, 1986-1988 (Box 563, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Cornell University and the International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 71-71A: March 15, 1983-March 14, 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 563, Folder 5)
- IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers), Publication (Box 564, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 564, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 564, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Attached is our 'Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Agreements between the New York City Board of Education and the International Unio o fOperating Engineers., 1983; Publication (Box 564, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Engineer agreement between Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Incorporated and Local 94-94A-94B, International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO: Effective: January 1, 1984 to December 31, 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 564, Folder 1)
    Author: IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers); Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Inc.
  - Item 5: Agreement by and between the State of Alaska and Alaska Public Service Employees, Local #71 (AFL-CIO) covering Labor, Trades, and Crafts Unit Employees: 1976, Publication (Box 564, Folder 1)
    Author: Alaska Public Service Employees. Local 71; State of Alaska
  - Item 6: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, Douglas Aircraft Company, Component of McDonnell Douglas Corporation and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local No. 501: effective date: February 16, 1981: expiration date: December 4, 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 564, Folder 1)
    Author: McDonnell Douglas Corporation; IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers). Local 501
  - Item 7: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, Douglas Aircraft Company, and McDonnell Douglas Astronautics Company Huntington Beach, components of McDonnell Douglas Corporation and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 501 (Weldors): effect, 1981-1983 (Box 564, Folder 1)
- IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers), Publication (Box 564, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Attached is our "Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Ageement Between the New York City Board of Education and the International UnionLocal 891, 1979; Publication (Box 564, Folder 2)
    Author: Sidney Schwartz
  - Item 2: The Engineer - vol. 8, no. 2 (Sept. 1987), Publication (Box 564, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1987:Sep.)
  - Item 3: Background and position papers, 1983 International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO: manual, Publication (Box 564, Folder 2)
    Author: IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers); AFL-CIO, Department of Education
- Oregon State Employes Association, Publication (Box 564, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1977; Publication (Box 564, Folder 3)
    Author: Oregon State Employes Association
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws, 1988; Publication (Box 564, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Constitution and by-laws, 1990; Publication (Box 564, Folder 3)
- Oregon AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 564, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Legislative Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 564, Folder 4)
    Author: Oregon AFL- CIO
    Notes: v.12:no.5 (1981:feb. 16)
  - Item 2: A brief history of the Oregon State Employees' Association: revision and continuation 5-8-43 through 10-21-72, 1973; Publication (Box 564, Folder 4)
    Author: J. Lloyd LeMaster
- International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 564, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Settlement of 1991 negotiations: Memorandum of agreement, Publication (Box 564, Folder 5)
    Author: Magma Copper Company; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; United Steel Workers of America; United Transportation Union.
  - Item 2: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, McDonnell Douglas Astronautics Company, Huntington Beach, Component of McDonnell Douglas Corporation District Council of Painters No. 36, Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, AF, 1980-1983 (Box 564, Folder 5)
    Author: McDonnell Douglas Corporation; McDonnell Douglas Astronautics Company; Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining agreement between Paint, Varnish, Lacquer and Allied Products Union, Local 1482, International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, AFL-CIO and Paint Manufacturers' Exchange, Inc.: Dated: May 1, 1971, Publication (Box 564, Folder 5)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades; Paint Manufacturers' Exchange, Inc.; Paint, Varnish, Lacquer and Allied Products Union, Local 1482
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining agreement between Paint, Varnish, Lacquer and Allied Products Union, Local 1482, International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, AFL-CIO and Paint Manufacturers' Exchange, Inc.: Dated: May 1, 1971, Publication (Box 564, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Cornell University and Tompkins-Cortland Counties Building Trades Council, Maintenance Division: July 1, 1986-June 30, 1989, 1986-1989 (Box 564, Folder 5)
    Author: Cornell University; Building Trades Council of Tompkins-Cortland Counties (New York State)
- International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 564, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1985; Publication (Box 564, Folder 6)
    Author: Painters and Allied Trades
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1995; Publication (Box 564, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1995; Publication (Box 564, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Painter and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, 1986; Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Painter and Allied Trades
  - Item 2: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, 1986; Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, 1993; Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, 1993; Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, 1980; Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Directory of Secretaries and Business Representatives, 1980; Publication (Box 565, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Painter and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: This is your union, Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: If you really want to make it, Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: IBPAT/OSH Project: "No-Name Hospital" Quiz, Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Spotlite News, 1977; Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1977:Dec.).
  - Item 5: Spotlite News, 1977; Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1977:Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: IBPAT-OSH Health and Safety Program - Catalog, Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Product Labeling Letters From Members, 1980; Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
    Notes: Loose leaf binder with articles and copies of letters from employees hurt on the job
  - Item 8: P.A.T.: check-off handbook, Publication (Box 565, Folder 2)
- UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union), Publication (Box 565, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Basic hourly wage rate schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 565, Folder 3)
    Author: UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union); IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers)
  - Item 2: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Pine Bluff Mill and United Paperworkers International Union and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: December 1, 1984 through August 31, 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 565, Folder 3)
    Author: International Paper Company; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union); IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers)
  - Item 3: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Texarkana Mill and United Paperworkers International Union, AFL-CIO-CLC and Local Unions 1148 & 1149: December 1, 1973 through November 30, 1977, 1973-1977 (Box 565, Folder 3)
    Author: International Paper Company; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union)
  - Item 4: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Georgetown Mill and United Paperworkers International Union, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: January 12, 1982 through May 31, 1986, 1982-1986 (Box 565, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Texarkana Mill and United Paperworkers International Union, AFL-CIO-CLC and Local Unions 1148 & 1149: December 1, 1977 through November 30, 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 565, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Androscoggin Mill, Jay, Maine and United Paperworkers International Union and International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1984; Publication (Box 565, Folder 3)
    Author: International Paper Company; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union); International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers
  - Item 7: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company and United Paperworkers International Union, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: June 1, 1979 through May 31, 1983, 1979-1983 (Box 565, Folder 3)
- UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union), Publication (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Hudson River Mill, Corinth, New York and United Paperworkers International Union and International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1984; Publication (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company and United Paperworkers International Union, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: June 1, 1983 through May 31, 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company and United Paperworkers International Union, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: June 1, 1983 through May 31, 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Texarkana Mill and United Paperworkers International Union, AFL-CIO-CLC and Local Unions 1148 & 1149: December 1, 1979 through November 30, 1982, 1979-1982 (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Basic hourly wage rate schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Pulp and Paper Group, Ticonderoga Mill and United Paperworkers International Union: Effective June 1, 1983, Publication (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Pulp and Paper Group, Ticonderoga Mill and United Paperworkers International Union: Effective June 1, 1983, Publication (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Agreement between Continental Can Company, Inc., Plant #502, Cambridge, Plant #513, Cleveland, Plant #516, Teterboro and United Paperworkers International Union, AFL-CIO, Local #461, Cambridge, Massachusetts, Local #386, Cleveland, Ohio, Local #1275, Tete, 1974; Publication (Box 565, Folder 4)
    Author: Continental Can Company; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 461 (Cambridge, Mass.); UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 386 (Cleveland, Ohio); UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 1275 (Teterboro, NJ)
  - Item 9: Labor agreement between the Hudson Pulp & Paper Corp, Palatka Florida and United Paperworkers International Union, Palatka Local 598, Putnam Local 641, Palatka Local 852, Palatka Local 1565, Bass Capital Local 171 all affiliated with AFL-CIO: June 1, 1974, Publication (Box 565, Folder 4)
    Author: Hudson Pulp and Paper Corp.; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 598 (Palatka, Florida); UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 641; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 852; UPIU (United Paperworkers Inte
- UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union), Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New Rules on Corporate and Union Political funds, Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Author: UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union)
  - Item 2: Promises, Pledges, and Pats on the back aren't enough!, Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between 3M and the United Paperworkers International Union, Local 186, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: 1981-1984 (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Author: UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union); 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company, Harford City, Indiana and the United Paperworker's International Union, Local 186, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: 1977-1981 (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Labor agreement between Hudson Pulp and Paper Corp., Southern Woodlands Division, Palatka, Florida and United Paperworkers International Union and its affiliated Local 598, AFL-CIO: Representing employees of the Hudson Southern Woodlands Division: June 1, 1974-1977 (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Author: Hudson Pulp and Paper Corp.; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 598 (Palatka, Florida)
  - Item 6: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, White Papers Group, Ticonderoga Mill and United Paperworkers International Union: Effective June 1, 1979, Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Articles of Agreement, March 7, 1974 - March 7, 1977, Diamond International Corporation, Packaging Products Division, Norwood, Ohio and the United Paperworkers International Union, A.F.L., Local 98, 1974-1977 (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Author: Diamond International Corporation; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 98 (Norwood, Ohio)
  - Item 8: Your rights under the new Federal Asbestos standards, 1991; Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Author: United Health and Safety Department
  - Item 9: Your rights under the new Federal Asbestos standards, 1991; Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: PEPworks for you, Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Labor agreement between International Paper Company, Pineville Kraft Mill and the United Paperworkers International Union, AFL-CIO and its Local Union No. 351: October 11, 1982 through October 10, 1986, 1982-1986 (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Author: International Paper Company; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). b Local 351 (Pineville, Louisiana)
  - Item 15: American Can Company, Green Bay Mill and United Paperworkers International Union, Local #327 and Local #213: Effective May 1, 1976 through April 30, 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Author: UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 327; UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union). Local 213; American Can Company
  - Item 16: American Can Company, Green Bay Mill and United Paperworkers International Union, Local #327 and Local #213: Effective May 1, 1978 through April 30, 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: UPIU Voluntary PEP Check-Off Authorization card, Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Notes: Blank form
  - Item 18: UPIU Voluntary PEP Check-Off Authorization card, Publication (Box 566, Folder 1)
    Notes: Blank form. Copy 2.
- UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union), Publication (Box 566, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: QWL: buzzword or breakthrough?, Publication (Box 566, Folder 2)
    Author: Edward Cohen-Rosenthal; Cynthia Burton
  - Item 2: 100 years of challenge and progress, Publication (Box 566, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Handbook of pensions under collective bargaining agreements: United Paperworker's International Union, Joseph P. Tonelli, President, Publication (Box 566, Folder 2)
    Author: Joseph P. Tonelli
- UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union), Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Help Us Beat the Corporate Thugs!, 1994; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The EAP Story: helping workers to help themselves, 1986; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: This is I.P. Country, 1988; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Striking out in the '80s, 1989; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Author: Kirk Victor
    Notes: Article from National Journal, January 7, 1989. Photocopy
  - Item 5: News from the War Zone: Staley Workers' Solidarity Report, 1995; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1995:Oct./Nov.)
  - Item 6: Stiking paperworkers say: Something smells wrong at Avon, Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: Includes boycott postcard
  - Item 7: Stiking paperworkers say: Something smells wrong at Avon, Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: Includes boycott postcard. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Stiking paperworkers say: Boycott PNC, Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Stiking paperworkers say: Boycott PNC, Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Paperworkers fight corporate greed, Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Paperworkers fight corporate greed, Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: UPIU Local 7837, AFL-CIO For nine months 760 families in Decatur, Illinois have been the victims of a cruel lock-out, 1994; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: Includes State Farm and Miller Beer boycott material
  - Item 13: UPIU Local 7837, AFL-CIO For nine months 760 families in Decatur, Illinois have been the victims of a cruel lock-out, 1994; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: Includes State Farm and Miller Beer boycott material. Copy 2
  - Item 14: UPIU Local 7837, AFL-CIOThe lockout of the 760 workers at the A.E. Staley Manufacturing Company has entered its tenth month, and although the members are suffering from severe hardships, so is the company, 1994; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: The Paperworker, 1991; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.5 (1991:May)
  - Item 16: To All UPIU members in the 26th Congressional District: Our Congressman, Maurice Hinche, has been targeted by the Republican party and is in one of the toughest fights of his career., 1994; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Author: Mario Scarselletta, Jr.
  - Item 17: Blade and Stone, 1995; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: January, 1995.
  - Item 18: They talk now, 1991; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Update on the International Paper Boycott, 1991; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Dear Faculty Member: Please take a minute to read through the contents of this packet., 1991; Publication (Box 566, Folder 3)
    Notes: Publicity Packet
- United Paperworkers of America, Publication (Box 566, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Manual for UPA-AFL-CIO volunteer organizers, 1956; Publication (Box 566, Folder 4)
    Author: United Paperworkers of America
- Patrolmen's Benevolent Association of the City of New York, Publication (Box 566, Folder 5)